NETFLIX PRESENTS
♪ Maybe ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ I will find a place ♪
♪ Which won't make me shiver ♪
♪ A space ♪
♪ To call my own ♪
♪ Where we could live forever ♪
♪ Sometimes ♪
♪ Time is like a medicine ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ A bright light guiding you home ♪
♪ But I don't know ♪
♪ If we could find our way back there ♪
♪ Will I ever be worthy of your tears? ♪
I miss her.
♪ So when you're lonely... ♪
We were always there for each other
in the most important moments.
♪ And on your darkest days... ♪
The war between our families
will be bloody.
And no one will emerge victorious from it.
Lots of bad things have happened,
but it would be good for us
to forget about this, uh...
unfortunate incident.
Unfortunate incident?
Oh, excuse me.
I should have said, "after this tragedy."
She wouldn't be happy... seeing you crying.
Look, I'll tell you one time,
and I won't say it again.
This is Sicily.
It's my territory.
You will never step a foot in here again.
I will make sure of it.
If you break the rule,
I will turn your ridiculous island
into a graveyard.
Tell them
to get the fuck out of here. Now.
Take your dog...
and leave.
You have one hour.
One.
♪ And losing faith ♪
♪ And on your darkest days ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Even when I'm gone ♪
I had something to do.
All right, I'm coming.
I've missed you so much.
It's too soon.
The doctor said that it's too soon.
I don't care what the doctor said.
Baby...
Baby?
I know how I feel, and I know what I need.
And it's definitely not lying in a bed
and feeling sorry for myself.
Bang, bang!
No way! Look at you!
You made it downstairs!
But shouldn't you be resting?
What is it with you and resting?
I've had enough rest
to last me a lifetime.
I'm tired of lying in bed
and having you baby me.
Raquel,
please bring us a bottle of wine.
Ooh.
That's hardcore.
It's not even 11:00 yet.
That's bad, even for me.
Need I remind you that you almost died?
- Getting drunk at breakfast is a bad idea.
- For fuck's sake.
Why does everyone suddenly
think they know what I need?
Do you have any idea
what we've been through?
Thank you.
I've never been so afraid of losing you.
And Massimo...
...his heart nearly broke.
Olo, I know how hard it was for you
and I know you're worried about me,
but I've been given a second chance.
I want to make the most of it.
Besides, we haven't even toasted
to you changing your mind about marriage.
What?
Nothing.
I'm just happy you're here.
Oh!
More, more, more alcohol.
I can't look
at that hair sober.
Oof.
Uh, hello, Giuseppe?
Can we fix hair today?
Right now? Okay. Let's go. Let's go.
Yeah, we're coming!
Of course. Bye. See you!
Oh.
You have a meeting.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't wanna disturb you.
Could you come and see me
when you're done?
Excuse me.
♪ I'm so fuckin' wasted ♪
♪ Buildin' up a hatred ♪
♪ What d'you want from me? ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I feel like I'm bleedin' ♪
♪ All I want is feelings ♪
♪ Let me try believin' ♪
♪ But there's no longer happy afters ♪
♪ Once you step, you'll fall ♪
♪ Pray ♪
♪ 'Cause no one's comin' for us ♪
♪ Time's runnin' out ♪
♪ Roads are broken ♪
♪ Here forever ♪
♪ No way out ♪
♪ So pray now ♪
♪ Pray ♪
♪ 'Cause no one's comin' for us ♪
♪ Time's runnin' out ♪
♪ Roads are broken here forever ♪
♪ No way out ♪
♪ So pray ♪
♪ Pray ♪
♪ Pray now ♪
Be quiet.
- ♪ Pray ♪
♪ Pray ♪
♪ 'Cause no ones coming for us ♪
♪ Time's running out... ♪
I'm cumming. I'm cumming.
♪ No way out ♪
♪ So pray now ♪
♪ Pray ♪
♪ 'Cause no ones coming for us ♪
♪ Time's running out ♪
♪ Roads are broken here forever ♪
♪ No way out, so pray ♪
♪ Pray ♪
They are waiting for me.
Wow.
So you're ready to go, then.
You just had sex.
And what makes you say that?
You're not wearing any panties.
But that's not the only thing.
Your hair...
and your lipstick.
So what? We bumped into each other...
"And I fucked him."
Yes, I fucked him.
Listen, I want to hear
every kinky little detail, got it?
Quit smirking and come help me,
or we'll never get out the door.
I've already got
everything picked out. Here.
This one?
- Or this one?
- The black one.
- Hey! Stop!
- Tell me everything.
♪ This reflection is so faded ♪
♪ Feelin' like I'm empty ♪
♪ A ghost inside a mirror ♪
♪ I've only seen it lately... ♪
Lari!
Did you tell Massimo we were going out?
Obviously... not!
He doesn't tell me when he goes out.
Fuck. Well, this is gonna be interesting!
- Come on, really? This place?
- What's the big deal?
All the good restaurants
in town belong to the Torricellis.
Let's go.
♪ To love me ♪
♪ Don't let me wake up ♪
♪ Until I've found you ♪
♪ Oh, I don't wanna give up, yeah
When I wanna get back to me ♪
♪ The ghost in my mirror ♪
♪ Is sealing my fate ♪
♪ Oh, I know I gotta leave you
Find somebody that loves me ♪
♪ Me ♪
♪ Find somebody that loves me ♪
♪ Don't let me wake up ♪
♪ Until I've found you ♪
♪ The ghost in my mirror ♪
♪ Is sealing my fate ♪
♪ And faked me till I'm wasted... ♪
Now,
that's what I call a food baby.
Well, just more to love.
Oof.
Hello?
Hi, Busy Bee.
Wait a second, please.
Where did you get my number?
You know... I am who I am.
You know my roots.
So... how are you?
Why are you calling?
'Cause... I can't forget about you.
So, try harder.
Who was that?
- How was everything?
- Great. Thanks.
Thank you.
Tell me the truth.
Olo, sometimes the truth is complicated.
Lari, what happened on that island?
- He was just different.
- Who?
Nacho.
I ran away with him
after Massimo cheated with Anna.
Hold on. I thought
that was a plot against Massimo.
It was,
but I didn't know it at the time.
Nacho was like my... best friend.
Seriously? You saw the guy twice,
and now he's your best friend?
Whatever. I'm not here to lecture you.
Sure sounds like it.
Did you sleep with him?
No.
But he was there for me
when my whole world was falling apart.
He took care of me, and I felt free.
Okay.
I have to forget about him.
Oh my God.
You're in love with him.
Don't be ridiculous. He's just some guy.
Okay, come on.
We're going dancing.
♪ Kiss me like a stranger ♪
♪ Come and taste my flavor ♪
♪ You don't need no chaser ♪
♪ Just vibe on my danger ♪
♪ Kiss me like a stranger ♪
♪ Come and taste my flavor ♪
♪ You don't need no chaser ♪
♪ Just vibe on my danger ♪
♪ Kiss me like a stranger ♪
♪ Come and taste my flavor ♪
♪ You don't need no chaser ♪
♪ Just vibe on my danger ♪
♪ Kiss me like a stranger ♪
♪ Come and taste my flavor ♪
♪ You don't need no chaser ♪
♪ Just vibe on my danger ♪
♪ I can feel your body ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ It's in your eyes, I see you want it ♪
♪ You crave it, you need this, yeah ♪
♪ So come get it, I've got it ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been waitin' all night ♪
♪ I don't need something right ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- ♪ And I feel I'm pulling you in ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ You don't need another one ♪
♪ I'll be everything you ever want ♪
♪ Ever want ♪
♪ Don't need a heart tonight ♪
♪ Just want a body moving side to side ♪
♪ Don't think about it
Boy, just move for me ♪
♪ Move for me ♪
♪ Kiss me like a stranger ♪
♪ Come and taste my flavor ♪
♪ You don't need no chaser ♪
♪ Just vibe on my danger ♪
♪ Kiss me like a stranger ♪
♪ Come and taste my flavor ♪
♪ You don't need no chaser ♪
♪ Just vibe on my danger ♪
♪ Kiss me like a stranger ♪
♪ Come and taste my flavor ♪
♪ You don't need no chaser ♪
♪ Just vibe on my danger ♪
♪ Kiss me like a stranger ♪
♪ Come and taste my flavor ♪
♪ You don't need no chaser ♪
♪ Just vibe on my danger... ♪
- ♪ Just vibe on my danger... ♪
- Since when do you go out without me?
♪ Come and taste my flavor ♪
♪ You don't need no chaser ♪
♪ Just vibe on my danger... ♪
Since I was 18.
♪ Come and taste my flavor... ♪
Have you danced yet?
Oh, yeah.
A little, before Domenico
almost killed Olga with his tongue.
♪ You don't need no chaser ♪
♪ Just vibe on my danger ♪
♪ Kiss me like a stranger ♪
♪ Come and taste my flavor ♪
♪ You don't need no chaser ♪
♪ Just vibe on my danger ♪
♪ Kiss me like a stranger ♪
♪ Come and taste my flavor ♪
♪ You don't need no chaser ♪
♪ Just vibe on my danger ♪
Leave.
Stay.
♪ You're my reason, baby ♪
♪ Your eyes pull at my heart ♪
♪ In the dead of night ♪
♪ I'm searchin', I'm searchin' for you ♪
♪ Please be mine ♪
♪ Set me on fire ♪
♪ Tear me apart ♪
♪ Lovin' you is like I'm dancin'
With the devil in the dark ♪
♪ Come take me higher ♪
♪ I feel it inside ♪
♪ That you're my curse ♪
♪ My salvation, babe ♪
♪ Trust me this time ♪
♪ You're my reason, baby ♪
♪ Baby ♪
♪ You know how to make me lose my mind ♪
♪ Made me a prisoner ♪
♪ In your arms ♪
♪ I don't wanna see the sun ♪
♪ Set me on fire ♪
♪ Tear me apart ♪
♪ Lovin' you is like I'm dancing
With the devil in the dark ♪
♪ Come take me higher ♪
♪ I feel it inside ♪
♪ That you're my curse ♪
♪ My salvation, babe ♪
♪ Trust me this time ♪
Why don't you sleep?
I can't without you.
"I can't without you."
What happened on the island?
Baby, I think
that you are drunk, and, um...
Maybe we can talk about this another time?
Answer me!
You'd like to know what happened?
Your ex shot me.
What happened between you and Matos?
Nothing happened.
Liar.
You ran away with him when you thought
that I was cheating on you with Anna.
It would've never happened
if you'd told me about your twin brother!
My twin brother?
That twin brother
that told me that you were pregnant?
I wanted to protect the family,
and I knew what you would do
if you found out
that I'd lost the baby in the accident.
I didn't want to be
the cause of another war.
You had no right...
no right to hide it from me.
It was my baby.
It was our baby,
who died because of your enemies.
Because of me.
Wait a moment.
I have to clean.
♪ Midnight comes round ♪
♪ You come callin', baby ♪
♪ I wanna know the truth ♪
♪ So tell me who you gonna choose ♪
♪ I know you got way more on the line ♪
♪ To lose ♪
♪ But I need you more than I ever knew ♪
♪ Always said you know
What's better for you ♪
♪ So why you draggin'
This decision so long? ♪
♪ Choose ♪
♪ 'Cause I need you more
Than I ever knew ♪
♪ I don't wanna feel like that
And when we fight like that ♪
♪ I don't wanna leave like that ♪
♪ So let's just run it back ♪
♪ You and me, we're makin' waves ♪
♪ Let's not throw it away ♪
♪ I know he's pulling, babe, for you ♪
My God, you're so wet.
What's wrong?
Um...
I think I have a hangover.
Hangover?
No.
I think you're hiding something from me.
Mm!
Hm.
♪ You gave yourself to me ♪
♪ But almost nothing changed ♪
♪ I'll still feel the pain ♪
♪ I wanna feel like home ♪
♪ But you got no time for me, my love ♪
♪ I'm alone ♪
♪ All alone ♪
♪ They always told me
Never fall in love ♪
♪ 'Cause we should be together
And I still got hope ♪
♪ 'Cause we can make fuck-ups ♪
♪ It's only human nature
I don't wanna share you ♪
♪ With anyone ♪
♪ Movin' through the fog ♪
♪ There's no easy way to get back home ♪
♪ We can search for gold
But we wanna find the love ♪
♪ Everything is lost
But I know I'm gonna need you most ♪
♪ I still got hope, I still got hope ♪
♪ You gave yourself to me ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ But almost nothing changed ♪
♪ I'll still feel the pain ♪
♪ I still got hope ♪
♪ I wanna feel like home ♪
♪ But you got no time for me, my love ♪
- ♪ No ♪
- ♪ I'm alone ♪
♪ All alone ♪
♪ Back in the days
When we were a team ♪
♪ I used to have a dream ♪
♪ And now its feelin' all too real
My little baby... ♪
Sorry, maestro.
Rematch later?
Yeah?
What do you mean?
What?
And you're just telling me this now?
No. Fix this today.
I don't give a shit.
Massimo, what's wrong?
Giuseppe fucked up, as usual.
I've known you my entire life.
These kinds of things never get to you.
Either you're getting old,
or something else is up.
- Tommy.
- Yeah?
I'm out.
Emi, hi.
I will be in the atelier today.
Please expect me.
Thank you.
Hey!
Why the hell are you in such a hurry?
My marriage is falling apart,
so I'm focusing on my career.
Now, come on!
That's great,
but do we really have to walk this much?
I'm so over this.
♪ A thousand... ♪
- I like those colors.
- I know, but that's too fancy.
- Yeah, it's too much.
- Yes.
♪ In silence ♪
♪ Wait ♪
♪ Who's gonna take the blame? ♪
♪ I need you all the time ♪
♪ I wish I was good enough... ♪
[Olga singing off-key,
♪ That it is all over... ♪
That's Michele, but he's very moody.
Very.
♪ Now... ♪
Laura, do you realize
how much work we still have?
Yeah, and this is so perfect because,
you know, I will keep my head busy.
Check this out.
♪ Maybe when the time is right... ♪
♪ Us now... ♪
- The first one.
- It's great.
It has wide sleeves.
Got it! What about this one?
Ciao!
Hi!
Hiya, Mama Klara!
I'm getting married!
- Okay, Mom...
- Really? Congratulations!
- Like the dress?
- I'll call later.
Beautiful!
- My little...
- I'll call you. Bye. Love you.
Kisses. Bye.
- Bye!
That was nice.
♪ Look at us, look at us now ♪
♪ Look at us, look at us ♪
♪ Now ♪
♪ Words can be a little blurry ♪
♪ When you hide them in the dark ♪
♪ I can only see your shadow ♪
♪ I wanna hold you when everything stops ♪
♪ Maybe we will find a reason ♪
♪ Maybe when the time is right ♪
♪ We can meet the expectations ♪
♪ Look at, look at, look at us now ♪
The photographer
needs to be tall and handsome.
Why? 'Cause I say so.
Plus, if the photos are from below,
it'll look like we have double chins,
which we don't want.
Just like this. Click, click, click.
Okay, fine. He can be short and handsome,
but he's gonna need a ladder.
Olo!
Thank you. Grazie.
And then I'll plop my bare ass
right on the cake.
Shit, you're not listening to me.
I am listening.
What kind of photographer do I want?
One with his ass in the cake.
You're unbelievable!
I can't believe you!
Massimo, let's go.
I'll catch up with you later.
♪ I can't stop thinking
'Bout my addictions ♪
♪ Understand, I'm a sinner ♪
♪ When I go through hell
There are no rules ♪
♪ I'm a sinner, I'm a soul gravedigger ♪
♪ I'm a sinner
When you look at me, I pray to you ♪
♪ Make you a believer
When you look at me ♪
♪ I pray to you ♪
♪ Fuck society ♪
♪ Can't feel the gravity ♪
♪ I'm flying high, I'm lost in space ♪
♪ Give me eternity ♪
- ♪ Fuck society ♪
- On your knees.
♪ Give me eternity ♪
♪ Can't feel the gravity ♪
♪ Fuck society ♪
♪ I'm flying high, I'm lost in space ♪
♪ Give me eternity ♪
♪ Fuck society ♪
♪ Can't feel the gravity ♪
♪ I want to take you higher ♪
♪ I want your dignity ♪
♪ Fuck society ♪
♪ Give me eternity ♪
♪ Can't feel the gravity ♪
♪ Fuck society ♪
♪ I'm flying high, I'm lost in space ♪
♪ Give me eternity ♪
♪ Fuck society ♪
♪ I want to take you higher ♪
♪ I want your dignity ♪
♪ I can't turn around ♪
♪ Oh, I'm losin', losin' control ♪
♪ Whatever happens now ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I'm ready, ready to go ♪
♪ I'll never fall ♪
♪ My mind is dangerous ♪
♪ When I feel alive ♪
♪ Got an open mind ♪
♪ I can't turn around ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm losin' ♪
♪ I'm losin' control... ♪
- Morning.
- Ma'am!
- Not now.
♪ But I know that at least I tried ♪
♪ When I feel the cold ♪
♪ I know I'm lost and... ♪
♪ Nothing can stop me right now ♪
♪ I'm a savage creature of the night ♪
♪ I'm a ghost, I'm whatever you like... ♪
I didn't know
you were coming early today.
Apparently.
♪ Don't tell me no ♪
♪ When I'm in the game ♪
♪ I can't turn around ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Oh, I'm losin', losin' control ♪
My new muse.
♪ Whatever happens now ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ I'm ready, ready to go ♪
♪ I'll never fall ♪
♪ My mind is dangerous... ♪
I guess I'll have benefits from it, yeah?
♪ I can't turn around ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm losin', losin' control ♪
Did you see the email?
Go on, read it!
We're going to Portugal!
Hey, girls,
it's only 9:00 a.m.,
and you're already drunk.
Um, yeah,
because we're going to Lagos Fashion Fair.
- Uh, for the fashion fair.
- Yes.
Oh, that's wonderful.
Look.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Ah! Oh!
Sorry, sorry. Oh.
I'm here.
Sorry, I couldn't leave amore mio
with a hard-on.
And now... what happens
in Lagos stays in Lagos!
♪ Lights come on when I'm around you ♪
♪ You got everything I need ♪
♪ So, baby, follow my lead, yeah ♪
♪ So let me try to achieve ♪
♪ Your love ♪
♪ Your love, girl ♪
♪ Why don't we turn out
All the lights now? ♪
♪ Yeah, I'm all about the dark love ♪
♪ Let's not think about the outcome ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm gonna put the blame ♪
♪ On me, on me ♪
♪ Don't you worry, it's on me, babe ♪
♪ All I wanna do is ♪
♪ Move with you, move with you ♪
♪ So, baby, let me put the blame on me ♪
♪ On me, on me... ♪
- They were in the villa the entire time?
- The whole day, why?
♪ Just fall in love with you ♪
He didn't even come to say goodbye?
I don't think we can fix this.
♪ Just fall in love with you ♪
♪ Lights come on when I'm around you ♪
♪ I got everything you need ♪
♪ I got you pulling at the sheets ♪
♪ I'll make you drop to your knees ♪
♪ To get me, to get me, boy ♪
How much longer?
Nailed it.
♪ Now you've left
I'm feelin' kinda frozen ♪
♪ Immobile ♪
♪ Now that all that's left of us
Is broken ♪
♪ I'm folding ♪
♪ Everything I knew ♪
♪ Was based on me and you ♪
♪ I'm searching
For the traces of a heartbeat ♪
♪ I can't find it ♪
♪ You never let me get my breath back... ♪
You're such a drunk.
Are you trying
to fucking scare me to death?
What are you wearing?
You're going out drinking with me in this?
Olo, I'm exhausted!
We've got a big meeting tomorrow.
I want to rest.
I can't believe you!
- Weren't you the one talking about change?
- Watch me.
- "I'm back from the dead!"
- Look at me. I'm lying down.
- Wait, what was it you said?
- I'm beginning to live.
What a poet.
Shame you don't practice what you preach.
- Get up! I'm not sitting around all day!
- Ola, no!
- You have one minute!
- You're crazy!
- The clock is ticking! Sixty!
- Olo!
- Fifty-nine, fifty-eight...
Hey,
the view's pretty good down here.
- Olo?
- What?
Aren't you engaged?
Pfft.
I'm just looking.
Ah.
His board's nice too.
Hey, cocktails.
Thank you.
I don't get it.
How can you be that into
messing up your hair in the waves?
- There's something primal about it.
- What?
It's just you and the water.
What? You and the water?
What are you, a surfing guru?
Have you ever even stood on a board?
- Yeah.
- When?
This one time.
Except I spent most of my time
in the water.
Why am I not surprised?
Now give it up
for our champion, Marcelo Nacho Matos!
Whoo-hoo!
What?
Olo, we have to go.
- Are you crazy? We just got here.
- We have to leave now.
What's up with you?
That's him.
Who?
- Nacho.
- What nachos?
The guy who got me from the ball.
He can't see me.
- Here he comes.
- What?
- Walking towards us.
- Here?
No.
- Oh, wait, he is.
- Let's go.
Shush.
- He's with some chick.
- What chick?
- Blonde. Cute. Nice legs...
- What?
She's pretty hot.
- That's his sister Amelia.
- You met his sister?
- What about his mom? Grandma too?
- Stop it.
- Olo, I have to get out of here.
- I'll shield you with my body.
Go, now.
Whoo-hoo!
I love surfing, so, so much!
Go, quick.
Bravo! Whoo!
I don't fucking believe it!
Now tell me everything.
I want every little detail.
♪ When the night is falling ♪
♪ Come and whisper to my ear ♪
♪ Like a ghost in my head ♪
♪ Go through my veins ♪
♪ Take my soul away ♪
♪ Ooh, I'm gonna cast a spell ♪
♪ And let it burn ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Like a ghost in your head ♪
♪ Go through your veins ♪
♪ Take my soul away ♪
♪ So come and call my name ♪
♪ Come and call my name ♪
♪ Come and call my ♪
♪ We are the lightning ♪
♪ We are the flame ♪
♪ Talk sweet talk all over again ♪
♪ This is when our eyes meet ♪
♪ This is where our heart beats ♪
♪ As one ♪
♪ We are the lightning ♪
♪ We are the flame ♪
♪ Talk sweet talk all over again ♪
♪ This is where our eyes meet ♪
♪ This is where our heart beats ♪
♪ As one ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ Save me from the shadows ♪
♪ 'Cause they wanna eat my soul ♪
♪ Feel the touch of my hand ♪
♪ I'm taking you there ♪
♪ Your wish is my command ♪
♪ So come call my name ♪
♪ Come, call my name ♪
♪ Come and call my name ♪
♪ So come and call my name ♪
♪ Come and call my ♪
♪ Come and call my name ♪
♪ Take my soul ♪
♪ Away ♪
♪ So come and call my name ♪
♪ Come and call my name ♪
♪ Name ♪
♪ So come and call my name ♪
Fuck...
♪ Closer ♪
♪ Just wanna have you close... ♪
Over here!
Where? Hey, Lari. Let's go to the bar.
One cold beer,
served by a hot bartender, please.
The best local beer
for the gorgeous friend.
- Oh, thank you.
- You're welcome.
Well, Olo, that beer
goes really well with your dress.
I've been classy for over an hour now.
This is long overdue.
- One glass of champagne.
- Sure.
Champagne, champagne.
So bougie!
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Mrs. Torricelli!
Hi, I'm Maria.
We wrote to each other. Nice to meet you.
Uh, it's a pleasure.
But please, call me Laura.
Okay, Laura.
I'll show you around
and introduce you to a few people.
- Shall we?
- Yeah, okay.
You coming?
Hey.
What's up?
♪ Closer ♪
♪ Just wanna have you close ♪
♪ Close, just wanna have you ♪
♪ Closer ♪
♪ Just wanna have you close ♪
♪ I just wanna have you ♪
♪ Closer ♪
♪ I just wanna have you... ♪
- Another beer, please.
- Come, please.
No!
No, no! Please! Please!
Darling! Please!
Let go of me, for fuck's sake!
What the hell is this?
Please!
♪ Save your words for later ♪
♪ Keep it slow ♪
♪ Love without thinking ♪
♪ Let's just let it flow ♪
♪ Show me a love like one... ♪
Laura? You look amazing!
Oh my God, Amelia.
Oh my God.
And that dress! Where is this from?
Um, it's from my new collection.
Actually, the first one.
No way.
When I'm gonna be back in shape,
I'm gonna become
your most faithful client, I swear.
- Girl, you rock it.
- Thank you.
Look at this.
Oh yeah, that's nice.
I think
you would look great in it.
Wow. Amazing.
It's beautiful.
Let's go.
♪ Closer ♪
♪ Just wanna have you ♪
Let go of me!
Mrs. Olga, please stop.
Vittorio, listen.
I'll go to my room by my own.
Mrs. Torricelli told me
to lock you in your room.
What? That rat!
Go.
Mrs. Tortellini
can kiss my ass!
Stay here!
Fuck!
I'm glad to see you in good shape.
I was really worried about you.
But you know, not only me.
You know, my brother
was like a shadow of a man.
♪ To hit me with your fever ♪
♪ More, more, more... ♪
Laura, you know
he's not a bad person, right?
He's just...
He's just loyal to his father.
It doesn't justify the way he treated me.
I know.
And when I found out what he had done,
I didn't talk to him, like, for a week.
♪ You drive me crazy ♪
♪ Wish I was leavin'... ♪
I know he hurt you deeply.
But believe me,
he has learned a very painful lesson.
♪ Like you got a million ways
To hit me with your fever ♪
Hear him out at least.
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, lovesick ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ Bye, bye, why, bye, bye, why ♪
♪ Bye, bye, why... ♪
- Shut up! What are you doing?
- Oh!
I want to sleep!
Hello, my dear friend!
Do you have a local beer?
Shut up! I want to sleep!
♪ Need it ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, lovesick ♪
♪ La, la, la... ♪
Fuck me.
Okay.
Some friend she is.
She's out there getting laid,
and she locks me away in a hotel room.
Without a single drop of alcohol!
She'll pay for this.
There we go. There we go.
♪ Need it... ♪
Fuck! No stairs.
Help!
Hello! Do you hear me?
Can you help me, please?
Mrs. Olga, please! Back to your room!
I must go to Mrs. Torricelli!
What is wrong with you?
I want to go to the party right now!
Goddammit!
♪ You cut me like a knife ♪
♪ When you said goodbye ♪
♪ I am lonely ♪
♪ Are you lonely now? ♪
♪ We could fly away ♪
♪ But you broke me once again ♪
♪ I am falling ♪
♪ Are you falling down? ♪
♪ Oh, so many times ♪
♪ You tore down my ice ♪
♪ Then walked
When there was nothing left... ♪
How could you do this to me?
Everything was so perfect
until you showed up.
♪ And I lost my mind ♪
♪ I crumble to the ground ♪
♪ Since you let me go ♪
♪ I dream that you're the one I hold ♪
♪ In the moonlight ♪
♪ Under moonlight ♪
- ♪ I'm crying to the stars ♪
- I think I'm in love with you.
♪ How could we let it go that far? ♪
- Shh.
- ♪ Our time has come... ♪
Don't say anything.
♪ Kill this love ♪
♪ Just kill this love ♪
I don't live here.
It was a mistake.
But we can fix it.
♪ Since you let me go ♪
♪ I dream that you're the one I hold ♪
♪ Under moonlight ♪
♪ In the moonlight ♪
♪ I'm crying to the stars ♪
♪ How could we let it go this far? ♪
♪ Our time has come ♪
♪ Just kill this love ♪
♪ Kill this love ♪
Make yourself at home.
Nothing special.
I know.
Come...
I wanna show you something.
You can run away from me...
but you can't run away from what you feel.
How do you know what I feel?
Your body is a worse liar than you are.
I need to go back to the hotel.
I will drive you.
You've already lost your way once.
Nacho...
I need time.
I will give you time, Little Bee.
I'll be waiting.
Even for the rest of my life.
Maybe you will have to wait forever.
It won't change anything.
My purse.
Are you sure?
♪ Oh, if my chest wasn't so hollow... ♪
Laura...
You think that I want only...
♪ And just watched me play pretend ♪
♪ With a heart made out of plastic ♪
♪ That needs a drink to play the friend ♪
♪ Leaves me sitting in the wallows ♪
♪ Once again ♪
♪ You always said that this was magic ♪
♪ Though I tried to feel the same ♪
♪ I knew losing you was tragic ♪
♪ But I couldn't feel the pain ♪
♪ You had me driftin' in an ocean ♪
♪ And I just left you with the strain ♪
♪ And now I'm sitting
In the wallows once again... ♪
I will love you.
I will protect you.
I
will never
hurt you.
♪ I chose hate, and I chose sadness ♪
♪ And you can never really cope ♪
♪ And now the wallows
Deep inside are all I know ♪
I wanna see.
What do you wanna see?
♪ I don't wanna waste another day ♪
♪ Don't wanna waste another day ♪
♪ In the wallows ♪
♪ I don't wanna waste another day ♪
♪ Give me some time, give me some space ♪
♪ Don't wanna waste another day ♪
♪ In the wallows ♪
Exactly this.
♪ Wish my chest wasn't so hollow ♪
♪ I'd have let this see no end... ♪
I want to watch it forever.
♪ Let's just play pretend ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I don't wanna waste another day ♪
♪ Don't wanna waste another day ♪
♪ In the wallows ♪
♪ I don't wanna waste another day ♪
♪ Give me some time, give me some space ♪
♪ Don't wanna waste another day ♪
♪ In the wallows ♪
♪ Oh, if my chest wasn't so hollow ♪
♪ I'd have let this see no end ♪
♪ If I had changed
Would you have followed? ♪
♪ Let's just play pretend ♪
♪ Someone like me ♪
♪ Said something that really hurts ♪
♪ And I need you ♪
♪ Remember me ♪
♪ And our memories ♪
♪ 'Cause I miss you now ♪
♪ Oh, I miss you now ♪
♪ But I know that we have got ♪
♪ To just let it go ♪
♪ Hey, I know it's complicated ♪
♪ If I'm not enough
You'll have to end it ♪
♪ I'd rather only one of us be all right ♪
♪ Hey, we should sleep forever ♪
♪ Can you say it's really better? ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't face
That you'll be with ♪
♪ Someone else ♪
♪ Hope, give me hope ♪
♪ Let me understand ♪
♪ Where I lost myself ♪
♪ Will I ever know the reason ♪
♪ Why I'm gone? ♪
♪ One last time ♪
♪ I'd change ♪
♪ I'd tell you where all my secrets went ♪
♪ I'm lonely, wish you were sorry ♪
♪ But it's lost ♪
You're worried.
For sure, Massimo got mad
because he wasn't able to track me.
If you don't want to,
you don't have to go back.
It would be the easiest way.
But at this moment, I...
Laura.
I'm not like him.
I won't force you to do anything.
You will always have a choice.
That's why I saved his life.
What did you say?
- He hasn't told you...
- Told me what?
When Anna shot you instead of Massimo,
she tried to shoot him again.
I didn't allow it. I killed her.
So you saved Massimo's life.
Why?
Because you love him.
Laura...
I don't want my happiness
at the cost of your suffering.
I want you to want me.
It would be easier for you.
Bee, you don't have to be with me
because you don't have another choice.
I want you to choose life with me.
I will wait for you... until you're ready.
♪ Hey, I know it's complicated ♪
♪ If I'm not enough
You'll have to end it ♪
♪ I'd rather only one of us be all right ♪
♪ Hey, I wish you stayed forever ♪
♪ And you say it's really better ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't face
That you'll be with ♪
♪ Someone else ♪
Where have you been?
At the banquet.
After the banquet?
I went for a walk, to think.
For a walk?
To think?
Mm.
You...
dirty...
liar!
Massimo...
I'm one step away
from asking you for a divorce.
Divorce?
What is this? New?
Huh?
Who did you talk to?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm talking to you. I'm talking to you.
When I got shot,
our relationship almost died with me.
I was trying to save it,
and you, you were speculating
and diving into your dark limbo,
which I was not allowed to enter.
Now I'm in my own limbo.
I don't know what I want,
but I'm alone there.
And I need space to find out what I feel.
Can you stop?
Stop!
Look at you.
Look at me.
There's no us.
This white shit has replaced me.
I'm going to leave it.
I'm going to sleep in Olga's room tonight.
And I expect you
to leave for Sicily tomorrow
to give me the time and space I need.
And do not think of following me.
Laura!
Fuck!
I return to Sicily.
The plane is to your disposal.
Whoo!
Well played.
You managed to lock this tiger in a cage.
Fucking hell.
Have you completely lost
your fucking mind?
You've gone crazy
for some dick you hardly know
just because he makes you wet?
What now, Lari? Hmm?
Well? Are you going to break up
your marriage and family for him?
I can't believe it.
You haven't married Domenico yet,
and you're already acting
like a Torricelli.
Spare me the bullshit
about family loyalty.
What am I supposed to do?
Wait until Massimo deals with his shit
and remembers I'm his wife?
Who are you looking out for?
Me or yourself?
Just leave me alone.
I have to figure out what I really want.
You're right.
I'm sorry I didn't ask how you're feeling,
or if you need anything.
Lari, look at me.
Look at me.
I love you.
I want you to be happy.
Whatever you decide,
I'll support you. You hear me?
I'm just worried.
Come here.
Watch out for my snot.
Remember, just say the word,
and I'll fucking kill both of them.
And I'll find you a nice, calm guy
from a village near Radom, okay?
That's right.
What?
You'll grow old and die of boredom.
Honey?
Hi, Dad.
Hi, sweetie!
I've missed riding with you.
Jesus, Laura, did something happen?
You came here on a motorcycle?
You're gonna give me a heart attack.
You know how much I hate your escapades.
Happy to see you too, Mom.
Come in. I've got some pork chops.
Of course, you never call ahead.
You could have told me you were coming.
I would have prepared.
I always have to think on my feet.
Honey, what's going on?
What do you mean? Nothing's going on.
I'm just here to visit you.
Your mom is convinced
that people buy motorcycles
when they're going through
some kind of crisis.
Honey, you'll be 30 soon.
If you were okay, you'd be spending
your birthday with your husband,
celebrating the anniversary
of your first meeting.
- As far as I know...
- I'm in love with someone else.
Uh...
His name is Nacho.
Honey, get me a cigarette.
But we agreed
that we wouldn't smoke anymore.
Please, bring me a cigarette!
All right then.
♪ I can lie to myself ♪
♪ I can say it wasn't me ♪
♪ But I loved it ♪
♪ You can say you are to blame ♪
♪ You can say it was escape ♪
♪ But we both know ♪
♪ Love won't run for us no more ♪
♪ Shadows walking past the door ♪
♪ I don't know if we'll make it home ♪
♪ Together, no ♪
♪ So maybe when we're old ♪
♪ And I come home... ♪
Honey, if you weren't married to Massimo,
who would you choose?
The problem is, I don't know.
When you have the answer,
you'll know what to do.
♪ There's empty love ♪
♪ Again... ♪
All right...
♪ I can lie to myself ♪
♪ I can say it wasn't me ♪
♪ But I loved it ♪
♪ You can say you are to blame... ♪
I'll tell you
a little secret.
I think it's what's kept
our marriage alive for 35 years.
Remember, a woman
must be selfish in a relationship.
If you put your own happiness first,
you'll do whatever it takes
to make it last, right?
You will cherish your relationship.
Mm.
But it can't be
a relationship that destroys you.
Remember that a woman
who lives only for her man
will always be unhappy.
Yeah.
And her man will be unhappy too.
♪ Walking away ♪
♪ Closer to sober ♪
♪ Something is telling me
We can't be reached anymore ♪
♪ I'm falling apart ♪
♪ But I know that I need you ♪
♪ I need you now ♪
♪ It hit me like a train ♪
♪ When nothing felt the same ♪
♪ Footprints in the waves
I can feel it that it's over ♪
♪ Something's gotta hold ♪
♪ I gave you ♪
♪ All I have ♪
♪ I wanna fall in the night ♪
♪ Shoulder to shoulder ♪
♪ I'll carry you ♪
♪ I'll carry with all that I have ♪
♪ Is there a word I can say?
Was there a chance in your head? ♪
♪ Is there a way to remind you ♪
♪ I gave you ♪
♪ I gave you all that I have ♪
♪ I'm running a maze ♪
♪ Further from home now ♪
♪ Something is keeping me
Following empty words ♪
♪ Is there light in the dark? ♪
♪ 'Cause I know that I need you ♪
♪ I need you now ♪
♪ It hit me like a train ♪
♪ When nothing felt the same ♪
♪ Footprints in the waves ♪
♪ I can feel it, that it's over ♪
♪ Something's gotta hold ♪
♪ I gave you ♪
♪ All I have ♪
♪ I wanna fall in the night ♪
♪ Shoulder to shoulder ♪
♪ I gave you ♪
♪ I gave you all that I have ♪
♪ I saw you out a couple days ago ♪
♪ Looks like you're already
Trying to change ♪
♪ I'm glad your color's back ♪
♪ Maybe time is what we needed ♪
♪ To find out... ♪
Thanks.
Ah, my coffee.
Okay. No lid for me.
Thank you very much.
Thanks. Bye.
Coffee for Dad. And for his daughter?
Mm.
- Lemonade.
Sometimes I wish
I was still that little girl
you used to take out for lemonade.
You'll always be my little girl.
♪ I just wanna hold you
Like the troubles are gone ♪
♪ Just wanna come through
When it's hard to be strong ♪
♪ You are my whole life
Whole life, yeah ♪
♪ Did you really leave town
'Cause it's somebody else? ♪
♪ Or was I not around
When you needed me most? ♪
♪ You are my whole life, whole life ♪
I like spending time with you
because I can eat as much as I want
and not feel guilty.
Yeah.
It's different with Mom.
- I've noticed.
- Hmm.
There are two things
you never point out to a woman.
What things?
Her age and the amount of food she eats.
I never knew about the second one.
- You should.
- Okay, I'll keep that in mind.
Excuse me.
- Just a second. Olga won't stop calling.
- Okay.
How's everything?
- Good, thanks.
- Great.
Hello. Answer my calls,
or I'll have a heart attack.
Jeez, Olo, relax. What's up?
You want to know what's up?
Massimo knows about everything, Lari.
He knows about you and Nacho!
He's gonna kill you,
me, and God knows who else!
Um, he told you that?
No, I overheard him
talking to Domenico.
Um, how did you know
what they were talking about?
You don't speak Italian.
Maybe you don't.
But I was pissed off
about not understanding, so I learned.
Maybe I'm not a fluent speaker,
but I understand everything.
You know how to say, "Nacho fucked Laura"?
"Nacho ha scopato Laura."
I guess it's time to go back to Sicily.
Are you fucking insane? He knows!
Shoot! Fuck knows what he's gonna do!
Fuck. I just said, "shoot."
I'd rather him shoot himself
than you or me.
Olo, stop. There must be a reason
he hasn't done anything about it yet.
Are you even listening to me?
Massimo won't forgive cheating.
- Listen.
- Shit.
I'm not scared of my own husband.
I won't hide from him.
I'm coming back.
Do what you want.
I'm working on... an escape plan.
Olo, relax. Have a cigarette, okay?
What the hell do you think I'm doing?
I can't stop smoking!
Okay, bye.
Dad, I have to go back to Sicily.
Okay.
But first, let's go back to the table.
I ordered some apple pie.
Come on.
English, please.
Mr. Fabio Rossi,
what did you not understand
when I told you not to push me?
Laura...
by coming here, I'm risking my life
and also my father's life in business.
We have a pact with Massimo
not to enter his territory.
And you know what?
I didn't give a fuck...
because I needed to see you.
Bee...
Please.
Hear me out, and then do what you want.
As you always do.
Okay, Mr. Fabio Rossi. Let's go.
You know the address.
You used to work there as a gardener.
I've already apologized for that.
I will do it again.
You wanted to tell me something.
Okay.
I want to be honest with you.
Since I met you...
I understand what it means
to be best friends with your lover.
I didn't fall in love with you
at first sight.
I came to like you first.
For the way you get angry...
the way you squint your eyes.
For being so stubborn.
I love looking at you.
When you sleep.
When you smile
without a reason.
When you brush your teeth...
and raise one leg.
I want it all, Laura.
I wanna discover new things with you.
I wanna show you the sunrise in Burma.
I wanna meditate with you in Bali.
And get drunk with you in Tokyo.
I know it sounds silly, but...
I have no idea
when you became my world, Laura.
I can't help it.
I can't live without this world,
and I don't want to.
I don't know how to convince you.
I'm ready to give you everything.
Whatever you want from me.
Thank you for finding the courage
to tell me all of this.
I know it wasn't easy.
But I also need to speak with Massimo.
I can't stay in that situation anymore.
Nacho...
I need more time.
I will wait.
You're here!
Okay. I packed just one suitcase.
I grabbed your stuff too.
It'll be a quick escape.
Why the fuck didn't you call or text?
I would've sent a driver for you.
My driver was really nice.
Are you serious? Now's not the best time...
Fuck.
Are you fucking crazy?
Have you forgotten your husband's
line of work?
Why don't you bring him with you,
and I'll look up how to send
a dead body back to Poland?
Happy birthday.
God, it's so sad.
You're going to die on your birthday.
Happy birthday, Lari!
If you survive,
I bought you a really nice bag.
If something happens, I'll keep it.
- Olo...
- Yeah?
Where's Massimo?
He went to the beach.
- Okay, I'll go find him.
- Really?
We need to work things out.
And when I get back,
we'll drink to my resurrection, okay?
- I have to go now.
- Yeah.
- Olo...
- Yeah?
- I'm doing this alone.
- Oh yeah, alone. I'll stay here and wait.
Fuck...
I'll just sit and wait.
Lari will be okay on her own.
Massimo...
We need to talk.
Let me start.
This conversation will be
much more difficult for me.
- Massimo...
- Wait.
I have to say it all now.
Otherwise, I'm afraid
I'm never gonna be able to say it again.
That time changed my life.
Not only because I had you,
but also because I realized
what I really want for myself.
I thought I could...
I didn't want to be bad.
I can't forgive myself
that you didn't feel to come to me anymore
after losing our baby.
That you had to deal with it all alone,
it has destroyed me...
you...
us.
So you knew everything about Nacho
for a long time, didn't you?
Why didn't you do anything?
When I was a child,
my dad used to read me a book.
I still remember one sentence,
a little parable.
I didn't really understand it back then.
But now I do.
"If you really love something...
just let it go."
"If it comes back, it's yours forever."
"If it doesn't...
it was never meant to be."
Your dad was a wonderful father.
And you also will be, one day.
♪ A thousand color paintings
You have made for us ♪
♪ When I'm down
I look at your photograph... ♪
Are you back, baby girl?
♪ Counting all the days
That we've been separate ♪
♪ I disappear and burn
Like my damn cigarette ♪
♪ I just wanna fall asleep
And dream of you ♪
♪ But listen, I wanna tell you that ♪
♪ You should never be scared ♪
♪ Whenever you need ♪
♪ I will be there
And it doesn't matter where or when ♪
♪ I wanna wrap you with my wings ♪
♪ And fly like angels with no fears ♪
♪ Chasing the stars ♪
♪ Until we get so tired
Then we nap on the clouds ♪
♪ In me, you will always find home ♪
♪ It's all about you, it's all right ♪
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ Two bodies, one soul, it's you and I ♪
♪ It's you and I ♪
♪ Mm, one day, you'll understand
What I wanted to say ♪
♪ I have no faults
And life's sometimes a little strange ♪
♪ But I can't stop walking
'Cause I live for you ♪
♪ Listen, I wanna tell you that ♪
♪ You should never be scared ♪
♪ Whenever you need ♪
♪ I will be there
And it doesn't matter where or when ♪
♪ Oh, I wanna wrap you with my wings ♪
♪ Fly like angels with no fears ♪
♪ Chasing the stars ♪
♪ Until we get so tired
Then we'll nap on the clouds ♪
♪ It's all about you ♪
♪ It's all right ♪
♪ Two bodies, one soul, it's you and I ♪
♪ It's you and I ♪
♪ Maybe ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ I will find a place ♪
♪ Which won't make me shiver ♪
♪ A space ♪
♪ To call my own ♪
♪ Where we could live forever ♪
♪ Sometimes ♪
♪ Time is like a medicine ♪
♪ A bright light guiding you home ♪
♪ But I don't know ♪
♪ If we could find our way back there ♪
♪ Will I ever be worthy of your tears? ♪
♪ So when you're lonely ♪
♪ And losing faith ♪
♪ And on your darkest days ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Even when I'm gone ♪
♪ So when you're alone ♪
♪ And losing faith ♪
♪ And on your darkest days ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Even when I'm gone ♪
Subtitle translation by: Maja Konkolewska
and Meredith Cannella